[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country consumes the most beer.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["The USA", "Russia", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What aircraft was used by the United States Navys Blue Angles demonstration team prior to adopting the F/A18 Super Hornet?", "correct_answer": "A-4", "incorrect_answers": ["Cessna 182", "A-10", "F-4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "About 95% of the rocks which form the upper part of the Earths crust are Igneous Rocks.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scientists estimate that the Earth and the Solar System were formed how long ago?", "correct_answer": "4.5 billion years", "incorrect_answers": ["100 million years", "10 billion years", "3.5 billion years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brooke and Megan are the names of the two mean girls in the movie Princess Protection Program.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Now tell your father not to teach you any more. Its best to begin reading with a fresh mind are words Miss Caroline addresses to Jean Louise, the narrator of this novel.", "correct_answer": "To Kill a Mockingbird", "incorrect_answers": ["North and South", "The Millstone", "Jerusalem the Golden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dog breed, which originated in Mongolia and China, has very thick fluffy fur and a blue-black tongue.", "correct_answer": "Chow Chow", "incorrect_answers": ["Jonangi", "Kai Ken", "Hokkaido"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Richard Gere is a direct descendant of the Pilgrims who came to the Western Hemisphere on the Mayflower.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the luckless lawyer for Cosmo Kramer in Seinfeld.", "correct_answer": "Jackie Chiles", "incorrect_answers": ["Jimmy Lee Cofield", "Joey Chadwick", "Johnny Childress"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would be from Asia?", "correct_answer": "610", "incorrect_answers": ["125", "505", "450"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Hammer in the  1988 movie Im Gonna Get you Sucka?", "correct_answer": "Issac Hayes", "incorrect_answers": ["Sam Jackson", "David Sole", "Eddie Murphy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the more common name for the superfood Vaccinium oxycoccos?", "correct_answer": "Cranberry", "incorrect_answers": ["Cauliflower", "Courgette", "Cress"]}]